<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mirna Majstorović - UX Designer and Web Developer</title>
    <description>I am prototyping web applications and designing and coding user interfaces in HTML, CSS and JavaScript. I like to make complex workflows simple, seamless, and pleasant and strive to deliver well thought-out designs, accompanied by clean, valid, reusable code.
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:15:36 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:15:36 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sketch and Keynote Love Each Other</title>
        <description>&lt;img style=&quot;width: 80%; max-width: 450px;  display:block; margin: 0 auto&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/sketch-keynote.png&quot; alt=&quot;Sketch and Keynote&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first thing that struck me when I started working with Sketch was - wow, this is so much like Keynote. Before that, I&apos;ve been using Keynote for a while as a prototyping tool for several projects and the experience was great - there were some limitations, but it is a very powerful piece of software and you can do miracles with it, and yet it is so intuitive and easy to use. But I did have to use some additional tools, it couldn&apos;t get the whole job of UX prototyping and UI design done.&lt;br/&gt;
The word spread around that Sketch was the thing for prototyping, so I decided to invest time to explore and master it, but it turned out it&apos;s a sort of extension to beloved Keynote - great :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being an advanced user of Keynote, I was exploring the differences between the two, what improvements Sketch introduced, and which areas Keynote covers better.&lt;br/&gt;
It turned out both Keynote and Sketch had some advantages over each other, and they perform the best when combined together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Design in Sketch, animate in Keynote&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sketch is a great tool for creating static design, but how can I simulate transitions in user interface on click on a button, or some other user action - how the sidebar slides in when user clicks the link, how the accordion unfolds etc.?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, Keynote has some advanced tools for slide animation, but they can also be used to simulate transitions on user interface. Simply copy the groups of elements in Sketch that you want to animate and paste them in Keynote. Keynote &quot;recognises&quot; Sketch elements and you can continue to animate them.&lt;br/&gt;
I will not write a lot about how the animation in Keynote is done - there is &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@_jshmllr/design-in-sketch-then-animate-in-keynote-c7f40e59f8f8#.3cdegczfm&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;a great article&lt;/a&gt; that covers that topic, and several available video tutorials online.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h4&gt;Tables and charts missing from Sketch&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tables proved to be a very important UI element in my designs - most of admin interfaces and more advanced business software interfaces are based on tables, because they are great for quick scanning and comparing different information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately Sketch doesn&apos;t support tables as elements - yes, you can draw them using other elements like rectangles and lines, but that is way too much work in quick prototyping phase, when you want to be able to easily add, remove or rearrange rows and columns. Same thing with graphs and charts, there is no simple way to create them in Sketch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is where Keynote comes to rescue. Tools for creating tables and charts in Keynote are powerful. 
You can create and style very complex tables, apply different backgrounds, borders, paddings etc. using Keynote, and when you are done, simply copy the whole table and paste it in Sketch, and voila, it looks great. &lt;br/&gt;
After it is pasted in Sketch, the table behaves like a group of rectangles, lines and text, so you can adjust it to some extent (e.g., you can&apos;t correct a typo in text because it is &quot;locked&quot;, but you can delete that text element and create new one instead). For some larger changes, simply go back to Keynote, make adjustments there and copy/paste again. Always make sure you saved the last version of your table both in Sketch and Keynote, because you might want to get back to it.&lt;br/&gt;
I found this process to be much easier and faster than drawing the tables in Sketch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img style=&quot;width: 80%; max-width: 550px;  display:block; margin: 0 auto&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/keynote-tables.png&quot; alt=&quot;Keynote Tables&quot;/&gt;&lt;small&gt;Advanced tables and charts styling in Keynote&lt;/small&gt;


&lt;h4&gt;So if Keynote can do so much, why even bother with Sketch?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although I am a big fan of Keynote, there are some crucial things it can&apos;t do:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;Changing slide/screen size&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keynote lets you set custom slide size, but if you want to change it later, you can&apos;t do it without messing up the elements, they get skewed. Artboards in Sketch are much more flexible - when you adjust the size of artboard, all elements stay how they were.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;Exporting individual elements&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can only export slides (with solid background), not individual elements, so it is not suitable for creating and exporting graphics. Whatever graphic element you create in Keynote, you will have to recreate in some other suitable software if you want to use it later in html/css.&lt;br/&gt;
Sketch saves you that extra step - all graphic elements you created can be exported individually, with transparent background. You can even export them as SVG, and apparently it does a great job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;Copy/paste instead of Symbols&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Keynote there isn&apos;t anything like symbols in Sketch - if you make a change on one element on one slide/screen, you have to manually replace it on all other slides/screens.&lt;br/&gt;
A good thing is that you don&apos;t need to adjust position of the element when you paste it, because when you copy something in Keynote on one slide, and paste it to another, it is positioned on exactly the same spot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my opinion Sketch and Keynote work great together, each contributing with it&apos;s own set of features, and because they are so similar, learning is much easier. At this point I didn&apos;t explore the possibilities of Keynote animation in relation to UI interactions yet, but if it turn&apos;s out practical for that purpose, these two tools make a complete and powerful, yet affordable package for UX/UI design work, and I will look no further.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;


</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 21:00:38 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2015/11/01/sketch-and-keynote-love-each-other.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2015/11/01/sketch-and-keynote-love-each-other.html</guid>
        
        <category>UX DESIGN</category>
        
        <category>UI DESIGN</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ProMDM Redesign Case Study</title>
        <description>&lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;ProMDM is a Mobile Device Management service - the kind of service that became necessary once companies started to integrate larger numbers of mobile devices (smartphones, tablets) into their IT environment.&lt;br/&gt;
First version of the ProMDM admin interface was designed as very simple and clean UI, but growing number of features required thorough redesign.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;project-image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/projects/large/promdm-new.png&quot; alt=&quot;promdm-new&quot;/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;




&lt;h5&gt;Subject Matter&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mobile Device Management is rather new service, that became necessary once companies started to integrate larger numbers of mobile devices (smartphones, tablets) into their IT environment. Each device owned by the company needs to be registered - enrolled into the system, assigned to the employee, equipped with various business applications, e-mail and wi-fi settings, authorized or restricted from certain services according to employee role. The system also enforces security measures e.g. whipes the device in case it is lost or stolen. &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h5&gt;Context&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First version of the ProMDM admin interface was designed as very simple and clean UI, but growing number of features required thorough redesign.&lt;br/&gt;
Redesign was tough - existing users were very satisfied with initial UI so the redesign wasn&apos;t supposed to mess up existing usage patterns. It is difficult to make improvements, but not change anything ;) but there are ways, so we put our heads together and came up with something even better than before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Interventions&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Interface layout&lt;/h5&gt;
 &lt;img style=&quot;max-width: 45%; margin-left: 2%; float: right;&quot;class=&quot;project-image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/promdm-old.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;ProMDM&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The problem with old layout was that it didn&apos;t use up the whole width of the larger screens - instead, it was concentrated in the middle, with navigation on top, and ever growing content and functionalities started to stack one below another. The interface started to feel cluttered and constant scrolling up and down was becoming the issue.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
Therefore we introduced new layout, with fixed vertical navigation on the left hand side where it is always available and can contain more menu elements than horizontal navigation, which left the whole right side of the screen available for content and functionalities.&lt;br/&gt;
Also, we introduced the additional right section/sidebar, so the content of 3 columns can be viewed and managed in parallel, with minimum scrolling. This layout is now much more flexible and resistant to future growth of content and functionalities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;Responsive and Adaptive Layout&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admins of MDM systems usually sit in the office in front of the largest screens there are ;) so they expect all of the most common functionalities to be available on first screen, which is not unreasonable, there is quite enough space for them it just needs to be organized differently.&lt;br/&gt; 
But it also turned out they sometimes want to use tablets, at least for some most common or crucial actions.
So we needed to figure out what those actions are, and how the layout can be organized to utilize the full width of the large screens, but to work on tablets as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we organized the content in 3 vertical sections - left dedicated to navigation, and center and right for content and actions - the center section contains the most important content and most common actions, and the right one is dedicated for more advanced actions and settings, or for contextual settings related to the item that is currently selected.&lt;br/&gt;
Middle column is always visible, and right column slides in and out on click, so user can show or hide it at his own will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;This is how the 3 columns interact based on available screen width:&lt;/h4&gt;

    
      &lt;h5&gt;Large desktop&lt;/h5&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
      Navigation is visible. Middle section has 2-column layout. Pulling out the right sidebar reduces the width of middle section (the two can be viewed in parallel).&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;a  style=&quot;display: inline-block; text-align:center; width: 100%;&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/blog/promdm-redesign-wide1.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;promdm-redesign&quot; data-title=&quot;LARGE DESKTOP - Navigation is visible. Middle section has 2-column layout. Pulling out the right sidebar reduces the width of middle section (the two can be viewed in parallell).&quot;&gt;&lt;img  src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/promdm-redesign-wide1.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;

      
        &lt;h5&gt;Narrow desktop&lt;/h5&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Navbar is collapsed. Middle section has 2-column layout. Pulling out the right sidebar doesn&apos;t reduce width of middle section, but overlaps it.
        
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;a style=&quot;display: inline-block; text-align:center; width: 100%;&quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/blog/promdm-redesign-medium2.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;promdm-redesign&quot; data-title=&quot;NARROW DESKTOP - Navbar is collapsed. Middle section has 2-column layout. Pulling out the right sidebar doesn&apos;t reduce width of middle section, but overlaps it.&quot;&gt;&lt;img  src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/promdm-redesign-medium2.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;

   
    &lt;h5&gt;Tablet&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;p&gt; Both left column (navigation) and sidebar are initially hidden. When pulled out, they overlap the middle section. Middle section has 1-column layout.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a style=&quot;display: block; width: 100%; text-align:center; &quot; href=&quot;/assets/images/blog/promdm-redesign-tablet3.jpg&quot; data-lightbox=&quot;promdm-redesign&quot; data-title=&quot;TABLET - Both left column (navigation) and sidebar are initially hidden. When pulled out, they overlap the middle section. Middle section has 1-column layout.&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/promdm-redesign-tablet3.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  

&lt;p&gt;This way all the actions are available on all screens (except for the mobile phones - it is not suitable for such complex user interface and not expected to be used by administrators), they just require a few more taps to reach them on tablets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;Reducing visual clutter&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;project-image&quot; style=&quot;float: right; margin-left: 3%; max-width: 40%; border-radius: 50%; border: 5px solid #fff; box-shadow: 0 0 5px rgba(0,0,0,.3);&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/promdm-icons.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;ProMDM&quot;/&gt;

The interface is packed with functionalities and there is no space for reinforcing text with icons, so we used either-or approach - each information/action is represented either with text or an icon.&lt;br/&gt;The new interface is simple and clean - whitespace is the main design element, with just a touch of gradients and shadows here and there. The icons that are left are colorful, visually prominent, because they carry important information or actions that need to be easily spotted.&lt;/p&gt;





</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 14:00:38 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2015/10/22/promdm-redesign-case-study.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2015/10/22/promdm-redesign-case-study.html</guid>
        
        <category>UX DESIGN</category>
        
        <category>UI DESIGN</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is UX Design All About?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What is UX design exactly and what is actual expertise of a UX designer? When we come to think about it, it&apos;s kind of fuzzy, isn&apos;t it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what we do know, or better said - feel - is the difference between good UX and bad UX, don&apos;t we? We feel angry when the product is not working as we expected, confused when we don&apos;t know what to do next, irritated when we have to fill out some enormous form with information that simply can&apos;t be relevant...&lt;br/&gt; 
On the other hand we feel satisfied, smart, sometimes even amazed, when we get through some complicated process without friction and question marks above our heads - somebody there really thought about how we will feel. Somebody that cares.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;project-image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/ux.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;ux&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So there it is, that is the first and most important characteristic of a good UX designer - they CARE about how you will feel while using the product. And from that caring all the good things follow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mission of UX designers is to empathize with you as a user, try to predict the context in which you will be using the product, how you will be thinking and feeling, in other words, try to experience it from your point of view. That way they can remove the obstacles in your way, answer questions you might have, put visual clues for you to easily find your way, organize and classify things to lower your cognitive load...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;Research&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So how do UX designers do that, how can they know so much about us?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Well, by using all means available ;)&lt;br/&gt;
Research is a good start - about subject matter, about similar products, about users - what motivates them, what are their habits...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Research can be done in different ways - one of the most efficient is interviewing, users directly or different people involved in product development - business owners, customer service consultants, etc.&lt;br/&gt;
Asking the right questions in the right manner is very important here, because human psychology is rather tricky - many times what we say is not what we actually do, but rather what we would like to do or we think we are doing, so it&apos;s essential to skip all the conceiving layers and get to the underlying truth.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;The other way UX designers can get to know the users is by studying their behavior in similar situations, with similar products - is there a particular way they are doing certain actions or achieving certain goals, do they have some preferences, habits...&lt;br/&gt;
Some really helpful stuff come out of this initial research, at least something to start from.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;Prototyping&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then comes the tricky part - how to translate these research results into a user friendly product? 
This is the moment when UX designer includes other members of the product design team, utilizing their expertise and experience (product managers, visual designers, developers...). UX designer shares all the insights from the research phase, and together they start drafting product features, copying best practices, combining them with new ideas, iterating, refining until they come up with a product design which seems like &quot;the thing&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;Testing&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is considered a good practice to exercise a lean approach in UX design, meaning not to go too deep into defining all the bells and whistles of the final product, but to outline main features into minimal viable product, something that is presentable to the users but won&apos;t take months and months to develop. The reason for lean UX approach is the fact that in this stage the design team still doesn&apos;t know how the users will react to the product, are all of their predictions and assumptions correct? The only way to find out is to test the main principles with real users - do they find the workflow efficient and logical, where are the possible pitfalls? Only after testing and refining is the product ready for the real world.&lt;/p&gt;
 

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2015 21:42:38 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2015/10/13/what-is-ux-design.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2015/10/13/what-is-ux-design.html</guid>
        
        <category>UX DESIGN</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PozitivaHub Case Study</title>
        <description>&lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;Pozitiva Hub is a web application that supports weekly offering, ordering and delivery process and related communication in CSA groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;project-image&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/projects/large/pozitiva.png&quot; alt=&quot;pozitiva&quot;/&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;Subject Matter&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CSA (Community Supported Agriculture) movement started in developed countries in 1950s, as a reaction to growing industrial food production and distribution, jeopardizing the survival of small organic farms. 
The main principle of CSA movement is direct communication between small family farmers and their customers and sharing the risks of ever so risky small farm food production. &lt;br/&gt;
In practice this is achieved by forming small sustainable groups of consumers around one or several farmers. The group agrees on the terms under which they will buy out the farmer&apos;s produce in following season - that way farmers have secured market for their products and can focus on field works in peak season. On the other hand, consumers know where their food is coming from and how it is produced (in most cases the focus is on organic).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;Context&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This web application was built for specific needs of one CSA group in Zagreb.&lt;br/&gt;
Before PozitivaHub, communication in the group was relying on free online tools - mailing list and Google forms. Farmers would create offers using simple Google form and publish it through mailing list.&lt;br/&gt;
As the number of group members and farmers grew, that process was becoming too chaotic - there were way too many mails circulating, mistakes were common and the whole organization required enormous human resources. Some kind of custom automatisation of the offering and ordering process became a must.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;Underlying process&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Farmers publish their offers to closed CSA group on weekly basis - the offer contains information about the farmer and his farming methods, product description, unit prices, ordering deadline, time and place of delivery and payment methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Customers create orders which are not binding (show the intention of buying, but the actual payment is not carried out at this point).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Farmers receive orders, collect and pack the products, calculate final price, deliver them to appointed location and time and collect the payment according to previous agreement with the group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;Why not some &quot;regular&quot; web-shop?&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first thought was to use some of the existing web-shop solutions, but after analyzing the requirements it turned out they lacked flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Orders in web-shops are binding and could not be different from what is actually delivered, which is a show-stopper for small farmers - they never know what they will find in the field, will there be enough for everyone, and handling &quot;exceptions&quot; would be too much of administrative work for them. Farmers need a simple way to modify quantities after they see what is available for harvesting, so besides &quot;ordered&quot; we needed a state &quot;delivered&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other issue was handling products that are sold by piece, such as turkey, squash etc. - the price for those products is usually expressed by unit (e.g. 10$/kg) but the farmers don&apos;t know in advance how much will the harvested piece weigh, so they need to be able to enter exact weight of the delivered piece and then get the total price calculated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;REQUIREMENTS&lt;/h5&gt;
After analysing all the aspects of the process, we came up with following requirements:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to application needed to be restricted only to group members - user registration needed to be confirmed by administrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 user roles were required - user (can view offers and create orders), producer (can create offers and orders) and admin. Superadmin would have been great, but because of the restricted (read &quot;no&quot;) budget, that role was discarded.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multytenancy - one app should support more groups (at the time another group was forming so the idea was to share the same app and restrict user access to offers according to group membership).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One offer must support multiple delivery locations and times&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic communication between farmers and buyers should be covered (messaging, contact info...)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Figure out the simplest and easiest way for farmers to publish their offers on weekly basis - taking into account different products and ways they can be offered (bulk, in package, by piece...) eg. how to manage the quantity and total price calculation based on such different inputs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UI should &quot;speak for itself&quot; - there were no human resources to cover in person education and support, so the whole offering and ordering process should be frictionless, fluid and easy to understand (taking into account various levels of users&apos; IT literacy)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interface needs to be responsive - it is expected users will want to check their orders status on their mobiles prior to delivery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Farmers should be able to create basic paper documentation needed for transport and delivery (Delivery Notes, Orders) and export Sales Reports in the form ready for further analyses (.csv documents) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h5&gt;LEARNING POINTS&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;Best UX design comes from deep understanding of the problem the product is aiming to solve, or &quot;Understanding the Problem is Half the Solution&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PozitivaHub is a successful product - several groups are already using the application and find it helpful, easy to use, with just the right functionalities that make their lives so much easier.
Understanding of subject matter, of users and problem it is supposed to solve is the first step in UX design process, otherwise it comes to tapping in the dark. Usually the understanding is gained by research, interviewing stakeholders, testing and refining and other useful UX design techniques. Much of that process was skipped here, or to be more precise, was going on for almost 2 years prior to actual app development, by being involved in the group organization. By working on this project I was a user, a business owner, a product manager and a UX designer all in one - can&apos;t get better than that ;) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This positive experience was for me a living proof that the saying &quot;Understanding the Problem is Half the Solution&quot; is 100% true.&lt;/p&gt;




</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2015 21:42:38 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2015/10/09/pozitivahub-case-study.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2015/10/09/pozitivahub-case-study.html</guid>
        
        <category>UX DESIGN</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
